Guide to the City and Regional Planning Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- City Planning Subject Files, 1873-2000; Series III
  - Zoning
    - Studies And Proposals
      - Proposed Amendments To The Baltimore County Zoning Regulations, 1968 June (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Zoning For East Providence, 1963 March (Box 44, Folder 10)